That the other Ravi yes yes, the
rest of the bus present there will give you all that
from his side if you
want to make an insurance claim then that
yes sir the camera is on
that Sohail from Vriddhi in some deep U for
watching a probe against how are
you all I hope you all must be fine wherever you are
care don't go and stay together and wash the
dry fruits we are going right now
my friend has met with a minor car
accident unfortunately and we are
going to apply for his insurance
which is behind Meerut
this may or may not be coming you can
see in the mirror he is wearing a white mask so
basically what happened was he was taking a turn at the corner
remember the Scorpio from the front and it hit his side or he
was perfectly fine from his side but this happens what can be done so what happened was
just his
front side Prem which is the right hand
side frame on that right yes the
Prem of the right hand side the bottom all of that
is broken Saunth and here the look of West Bengal is of
all over India  The role is that you have to make an
insurance claim within 2008, if there is a one-sided
accident, then for that we are
going there and we will show you
what happened and what did not happen and what means how, what happens, the
entire process which will be developed one by one
line, today I am going to
tell you all that if anyone has an
accident, then how will you
apply for your insurance and
how will you be able to make your bonds and
bigger bonds because what
happens nowadays is that many, that is, many
vehicles go to many agencies for
insurance, a lot of
things get processed quickly, but
if it is your turn for insurance and
something happens, then you are kept
running for a month or a month and a half, so such
things are a very bad thing, you should
not do it like that, the agency people
also check the emergency of Kolkata to see
how much time all these things take and this is the
condition of the car next to me and
this is my friend's car
and let's see that Rachna Duda Duda  From here
I am currently driving,
this is the car and it is his, so
basically this is what is going to happen, see brother, if
you keep any car then this is going to happen, brother,
now I think maybe that
Android and Top Hundred, is there any person left
whose car has never been dented
or scratched till date, this is a normal
thing and it gets scratched, so that is what has happened and
now director Amit Jain is taking it,
if you liked the video then please do
like this video and if you
want to support me, want to connect with me, then
subscribe to the channel, but it will go later, so
you will get notifications of all the videos on the front
and after that comes, if you do not
want to talk to me, then the Instagram
link will take you to the description from where
you can easily follow me, talk to me, the
result of which is we are going to drive now, but you will
directly meet you in the agency,
what is the process, what is there on paper,
show me all those things
first, I need to know, it seems like details
You need a bell, the one
sitting behind you is on a learning course, if you fell and
how did your body remain, you need
that app, Monday Pandey, I have it, there is
a brother sitting behind me, the cross is with him
and he has a valid learning license,
so it is not showing on that bed, so there
is no problem right now, but whatever it is,
you all knew it by going to the agency, what all
this is, what is the process, after going through it all the
head would reach the
agency and then I will come and talk to you,
tell me minutes and from when there is no
use in driving, you have not reached yet
and this is Chandannagar stand and
what to say about this place brothers, if you are
intelligent then a hint is enough, there is one
way Sanjay river, now there are next four-five ways, understand how to
cross it and people keep coming and sitting,
now do whatever you want to do and right now
we are going ahead and I took a little
cut from GT road because there is 5 ton traffic there, there is
traffic jam at many places, for
some time our
plan was to cut a little road and take a
shortcut from Tubelight  Use it because look, the
distance is going to increase by one kilometer, but the
advantage is that we will be
able to travel in it for more than the distance we would have to wait, which means
we will reach faster and we wo
n't even feel like kilometers etc. What is it, what is it
not, that
here people are looking at selfies,
what is their mood, what are they
doing brother, it is their life, what can we do,
life is not like ours, we are
happy with our life
brothers because the love you people have is
very much for me, it keeps me happy
and by the way, brother, just keep loving me,
we don't need anything else, we will do everything for you, but keep
your love intact and now
please, the army will shake everyone up, it will take
time, but we will definitely build our own building,
GT Road, Jhal Mod, etc., whatever it is,
and here is Hero Agency
and Buddha, but this is your Hero Agency, the
love is bigger than this, the people on your side, we do
n't know if there is a property or land issue
[Music] with
Ajay,
otherwise no one would stay here and the
vehicles parked here have stopped there
and this Mod  Etc. whatever is
there, let's go inside it from Ashtik
and see what it means, it seems that you have
document honey, after that you will get
a message that you have to
claim for the insurance of the car, how much
time has it been since you bought the car, yes
on WhatsApp, okay,
thank you
and fashionable from here you will have to go to Yagya
on WhatsApp and talk on WhatsApp,
after that you will see that you will get
Chinese slide show
200, this is Hero's workshop and
that if it is a deal then it is real,
because of that no, no, nothing happens,
you just feel that the person driving was
right or not, then this is Hero's
WhatsApp and now from here we will
meet the manager and find out what is the matter, what is it,
details are available here,
okay, in this, you have to make an insurance claim,
come, friend, it is
insurance, click on it, am I claiming insurance, am I claiming insurance,
yes, then it will be here after the insurance claim
and
information, write what all
documents etc. as far as we are concerned,
yes, camera,
which one is on,
500 at the moment  Let us see
what documents are required for the
car, the car is here, park it there,
where is it,
I will show you the car right now and what has
happened, what has not happened, so this Dada is
stuck with this problem
that it has completely
soaked me in that
this is the biggest
issue in
Lutyens all day long, every person is getting the
insurance papers of the car first thing in the morning
and when the car is insured, anyway it does
not matter whether it is insured or not,
advisor on Wednesday,
if it is
okay or not, then
reply that there is some manipulation in the pole, the
reader is in the
east and
according to the turn on, I will blow up the enemy of Jyoti Nagar, if there is an
email sensor problem then
where is it, everything is done, the thing is that its
front part is 1305 501
also, if you want then you can directly
check the gas, if there is some option,
otherwise, then you also have the time of Durga Puja, so it may take
some time, if possible, it will take about 15 days  We are
thinking about what we
can do and I will meet you, the
plan is to get the effigy
done only after Durga Puja because there is no benefit in getting it done now,
work will stop in two days
and after that the car of June will be lying idle
and friend if there is any problem then we are buying tea from this
and it is also running, it is not running like this, we will
put it in, we have to run, otherwise there is no
issue so wait and
see what it is saying, the FD moments light is this, it will be
coming in the camera well
and these two things, one claim and the
Nifty one, the
insurance people give it to you here and
whatever is left, you can
look after the Oscar and whatever is left, you will have to pay
from your side, if you
want to get an insurance claim, then
whatever was there, I told you
what is insurance related and what is
not, if you found this video useful
then please do like,
subscribe to the channel and press the bell icon,
you will get the notification of other videos at that time
and till then, catch up with me  If you
want to talk then
you can follow me on my Instagram in the description from here so that we can
talk to people
so I will meet you in the next video till then
bye take care and thanks for watching this
video is with you
[Music]